Women's Action Alliance Records, 1970-1996
Sophia Smith Collection, Smith College
- SERIES II. PROJECTS 1972-96
  - Coalitions
    - National Women's Agenda Project
      - Projects
        - National Women's Agenda Coalition
          - Projects
            - Women's Agenda
              - Administration
                - Mailings, 1975-79 (Box 205-206)
                - Marketing, 1976-78 (Box 206, Folder 2-7)
                - Materials for reporters, including questionnaires, 1976, undated (Box 206, Folder 8)
                - Newsletter Association (Box 206, Folder 9)
                - Notes and memos, 1976, undated (Box 206, Folder 10)
                - Questionnaires: National Commission on Working Women and Readers survey, 1979 (Box 206, Folder 11-12)
                - Proposals and reports, 1975-78 (Box 206, Folder 13-14)
                - Subscriptions, 1976-79 (Box 207, Folder 1-9)
                - Suspension of publication, correspondence and report, 1979-80 (Box 207, Folder 10)
              - Issues
                - Full run, 1976-79 (Box 208, Folder 1)
                - Marked copies, 1977-79 (Box 208, Folder 2)
                - Complete issue files: organized by date of issue, then within an issue, alphabetical by department or article (Box 208-226)
    - Women's Centers Project
      - Administration
        - Budget notes (Box 227, Folder 1)
        - "Building a Women's Center" report, Sylvia Kramer, undated (Box 227, Folder 2)
        - Development: concept paper, correspondence, meeting materials, funder research, proposals, 1980-81 (Box 227-228)
        - Historical papers on women's centers in the U.S., 1985, undated (Box 228, Folder 3)
        - In-house notes, 1979, undated (Box 228, Folder 4)
        - Project director Anne Bowen: correspondence, resume, notes, subject files, 1977-81 (Box 228, Folder 5-11)
          [see also National Women's Agenda Project- Staff, Anne Bowen]
      - Survey and directories
        - Client questionnaire: drafts, circa 1980 (Box 228, Folder 12)
        - Participants study, 1981 (Box 228, Folder 13)
        - Women's Center's Guide: draft, undated (Box 228, Folder 14)
        - New England (Region I)
          - Draft entries and drafts, circa 1980 (Box 229, Folder 1-2)
          - Mailing list, 1980 (Box 229, Folder 3)
          - Survey process, includes questionnaires, results, and tabulations (Box 229-230)
          - Final drafts (Box 230, Folder 3)
        - Mid-Atlantic (Region III), 1981: correspondence, questionnaires, and drafts (Box 230, Folder 4-8)
        - Site visits
          - Interview guidelines (Box 230, Folder 9)
          - New England (Region I), 1980-81: site descriptions, meeting reports, and notes (Box 230, Folder 10-13)
          - Mid-Atlantic (Region III), 1981 (Box 230-231)
          - Other regions: reports and notes (Box 231, Folder 4)
        - Workshops
          - New Haven Women's Liberation Center, 1980: includes correspondence, participant materials, evaluations, and questionnaires (Box 231, Folder 5-13)
          - Everywoman's Center, Amherst, MA, 1980: handouts, correspondence, participant materials, evaluations, and questionnaires (Box 231-232)
      - National Association of Women's Centers
        - Administration
          - Brochures (Box 232, Folder 2)
          - "Herstory of the NAWC," undated (by Sylvia Kramer?) (Box 232, Folder 3)
          - Incorporation, 1982-88: constitution and by- laws, incorporation papers, and IRS forms (Box 232, Folder 4-6)
          - Correspondence and memoranda, 1983-89 (Box 232, Folder 7-8)
          - Coordinating Council, 1984-89: includes correspondence, meeting materials, and notes (Box 232, Folder 9-17)
          - Development: funding letters, 1985-86 (Box 232, Folder 18)
          - Ex-Officio officer Sylvia Kramer: miscellany, 1988-89 (Box 232, Folder 19)
          - Financial and budget information, 1987-88, undated (Box 232, Folder 20)
          - Mailing list rates, undated (Box 232, Folder 21)
          - Membership and outreach, 1985-88: address lists, printed material, and membership applications, 1985-88 (Box 233, Folder 1-5)
          - Miscellany (Box 233, Folder 6)
          - Newsletters, 1987-88 (Box 233, Folder 7)
          - Notes, Sylvia Kramer? undated (Box 233, Folder 8)
          - Publicity packet: memorandum, 1987 (Box 233, Folder 9)
          - Regional representatives: lists, 1986-88 (Box 233, Folder 10)
          - Surveys: correspondence and forms, 1987-88, undated (Box 233, Folder 11-12)
        - Conferences: notes, correspondence, minutes, printed material, 1982-88 (Box 234, Folder 1-13)
        - International Women's Centers Project: contacts, reports, speech notes, questionnaires, printed material, 1981, undated (Box 235, Folder 1-8)
      - Job-Training Partnership Act and Women's Centers Project, 1987-88 (includes Jo Sanders, Staying Poor: How the JTPA Fails Women (Metuchen: Scarecrow Press, 1988) (Box 235, Folder 9-10)
      - Women's Centers and AIDS Project: correspondence, proposals, reports, and publications, including Women's Centers and AIDS Project: A Guide to Educational Material, 1988; and Gerry Pearlberg, Women, AIDS, and Communities: A Guide for Action, 1991 (Box 235-236)
      - Women's Rights Lobby Day, 4 February 1981: notes, reports, leaflets, fact sheets, attendee lists, and planning materials (Box 237, Folder 1-6)
- SERIES III. RESOURCES 1970-96
  - Information and Referral Services
    - Project SHARE
      - Correspondence
        - General, 1974-77 (Box 238, Folder 1)
          [see also Technical Assistance Program-Correspondence-General, 1978-80, and Reference Services-Correspondence]
        - Larayne Ewald, research assistant, 1976-77 (Box 238, Folder 2-3)
        - Linda Small, project director, 1975-77: general, advertising, and fundraising (Box 238-239)
        - Irene Zahava, librarian, 1975 (Box 239, Folder 2)
      - Meeting notes, 1973 (Box 239, Folder 3)
      - Reports, 1977-81 (Box 239, Folder 4)
    - Technical Assistance Program
      - Administration
        - Consultations: notes and miscellany, 1979-80 (Box 239, Folder 5)
        - Correspondence, 1978-81 (Box 239-240)
        - Wanda Wooten, Technical Assistance Coordinator: reports, memoranda, and conference and meeting materials, 1979-80 (Box 240, Folder 12-16)
        - Fundraising logs, 1977 (Box 241, Folder 1)
        - Meeting notes, unidentified event, 22 Sep 1978 (includes Donna Meade, Jane Williamson and Wanda Wooten) (Box 241, Folder 2-4)
        - Memoranda and evaluation re: dismantling Technical Assistance Program, 1980 (Box 241, Folder 5)
        - Proposal materials, circa 1977-82 (Box 241, Folder 6)
        - Reports and evaluations, 1979-80 (Box 241, Folder 7)
        - Press releases and program overview, 1978 (Box 241, Folder 8)
        - The Support Center: informational materials, 1977-80 (Box 241, Folder 9)
      - Directory project
        - Administration: minutes, progress reports, research materials, mailing lists, questionnaire drafts, 1978-79, undated (Box 241, Folder 10-15)
        - Completed surveys and compiled results, 1979 (Box 241-242)
      - Project Open Doors: obtaining CETA-subsidized (Comprehensive Employment and Training Act) positions for a coalition of women's service organizations, includes notes, correspondence, proposals, and hiring materials), 1976-79, undated (Box 242, Folder 3-18)
      - Workshops and conferences: lists, teaching materials, surveys, correspondence, notes, outreach correspondence and press releases, and proposals (Box 242-243)
        [see also SERIES II. Projects-Coalitions-Women's Centers Project]
      - Proposal Critique Service
        - Administration
          - History, 1979 (Box 243, Folder 15)
          - Correspondence, includes proposal materials, 1979, undated (Box 243, Folder 16-18)
          - Evaluations, 1979-80 (Box 243, Folder 19-20)
          - Promotion/media response, 1979-1980 (Box 244, Folder 1)
          - Summary and evaluation, 1980 (Box 244, Folder 2)
          - Volunteers: correspondence, list, forms, and meeting minutes, 1979 (Box 244, Folder 3-5)
        - Proposals
          - Arts
            - Crafts, 1977-80 (Box 244, Folder 6-8)
            - Exhibits, 1978-79, undated (includes The Dinner Party by Judy Chicago, 1978) (Box 244, Folder 9-12)
            - Film, 1976-81 (includes DES Wonder Drug, 1981; The DES, 1980; and The Dinner Party - documentary about Judy Chicago, 1978) (Box 244-245)
            - Multi-media, 1979 (includes Appalachian Women's Project, 1979) (Box 245, Folder 7-8)
            - Photography, 1977, undated (Box 245, Folder 9-10)
            - Organizations, 1976-80 (includes Council of the Southern Appalachian Mountains, 1976-78; the Feminist Art Institute, 1980; and Women Make Movies, n.d.) (Box 245, Folder 11-15)
            - Performing arts, 1977, 1980 (Box 245, Folder 16-17)
            - Publications, 1979-80 (Box 245, Folder 18-19)
          - Childcare, 1976-80, undated (Box 245, Folder 20-26)
          - Economic Development, 1976-80 (includes the Allcraft Foundation, 1980) (Box 246, Folder 1-17)
          - Ethnic & Racial
            - Association de Mujeres Puertorriquenas, 1978 (Box 246, Folder 18)
            - Black Women's Research & Development Center, 1979 (Box 246, Folder 19)
            - Cante Ohitika Win (Native American), 1976 (Box 246, Folder 20)
            - Lilith Magazine, 1977 (Box 246, Folder 21)
            - Native American Solidarity Committee, undated (Box 246, Folder 22)
            - White Buffalo Calf Association (Native American), 1980 (Box 246, Folder 23)
            - Women of All Red Nations, 1979 (Box 246, Folder 24)
          - Health, 1976-80 (Box 247, Folder 1-9)
          - Legal, 1976-80 (includes Female Offender Program, 1979 and Asian-American Legal Defense Fund, 1977) (Box 247, Folder 10-19)
          - Lesbianism, 1978-79, undated (Box 247, Folder 20-22)
          - Mothering, 1976-80 (Box 248, Folder 1-5)
          - Museums, 1975, 1980 (Box 248, Folder 6-7)
          - Networking/Organizing, 1976-80, undated (Box 248, Folder 8-17)
          - Older Women, 1977, 1979, undated (includes Gray Panthers, n.d.) (Box 248, Folder 18-20)
          - Political Activism, 1979-80, undated (includes National Congress of Neighborhood Women, 1980, and Welfare Rights Organization, 1980) (Box 249, Folder 1-7)
          - Reproductive rights, 1980 (Box 249, Folder 8-9)
          - Research
            - Feminism as Political Philosophy, 1979 (Box 249, Folder 10)
            - How Women Ran for Political Office in 1976, undated (Box 249, Folder 11)
            - Research on Appalachian Women and Girls, 1977 (Box 249, Folder 12)
            - Women and Religion: archives project, 1980 (Box 249, Folder 13)
          - Sexism, 1976-80 (includes Ysleta Equity Seekers, 1980) (Box 249-250)
          - Sports, 1976, 1979 (Box 250, Folder 6-7)
          - Violence against women
            - Awareness and Prevention, 1976-77 and undated (Box 250, Folder 8-14)
            - Crisis Intervention, 1976-80, undated (Box 250, Folder 15-22)
            - Shelters, 1976-80 (Box 251, Folder 1-12)
          - Women in Transition
            - Displaced Homemakers, 1979-80 (Box 251-252)
            - Education & Employment, 1976-80 (Box 252, Folder 3-14)
            - Women's Centers, 1974-80 (Box 252-253)
          - YWCA Women's Centers, 1979-80 (Box 253, Folder 12-15)
          - Youth, 1979-80 (Box 253, Folder 16-21)
    - Reference services
      - Guidelines and summaries, circa 1980 (Box 253, Folder 22)
      - Telephone
        - Reference log, circa 1976-77 (Box 253, Folder 23)
        - Telephone and library visitation log, 1976 (Box 253, Folder 24)
        - Telephone and correspondence log, 1977 (Box 253, Folder 25)
        - Inquiry reports, 1979-81 (Box 253-255)
        - Proposal, undated (Box 255, Folder 5)
        - Telephone reference messages, 1985 (Box 255, Folder 6)
        - Telephone log reports, 1981-89 (Box 255-256)
        - Visitor guestbook, 1993-96 (Box 256, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence
        - "Dear Alliance": compilation of typical letters, circa 1975 (Box 256, Folder 3)
        - General, 1971-87, undated (Box 256-260)
        - By topic
          - Abortion, 1971-81 (Box 260, Folder 4)
          - Business and economics, 1972-87, undated (Box 260, Folder 5)
          - Childcare, 1971-86, undated (Box 260, Folder 6)
          - Education
            - General, 1971-83 (Box 260, Folder 1)
            - Elementary/primary and secondary, 1971-83 (Box 260, Folder 2)
            - Higher and continuing, 1972-86 (Box 260, Folder 3-4)
            - Title IX, 1976-84 (Box 260, Folder 5)
            - Scholarships, 1973-86, undated (Box 260, Folder 6)
            - Women's Studies, 1972-81, undated (Box 260, Folder 7)
          - Employment: general and affirmative action, 1972-87, undated (Box 262-263)
            - Discrimination, 1975-82 (Box 263, Folder 3)
            - Displaced homemakers, 1976-84 (Box 263, Folder 4)
            - Management/starting businesses, 1974-83 (Box 263, Folder 5)
            - Unions, 1972-79 (Box 263, Folder 6)
          - Equal Rights Amendment, 1977-82 (Box 263, Folder 7)
          - Family issues, 1972-83 (Box 263, Folder 8)
          - Family violence, 1976-83 (Box 263, Folder 9)
          - Government and politics, 1971-83 (Box 264, Folder 1)
          - Health
            - General, 1972-86, undated (Box 264, Folder 2-4)
            - Psychiatric referral requests, 1973-76 (Box 264, Folder 5)
            - Obstetrics/Gynecology, 1972-73, undated (Box 264-265)
          - Legal Aid
            - General, 1971-87, undated (Box 265, Folder 2-6)
            - Credit, 1974-80 (Box 265, Folder 7)
            - Divorce, 1975-83, undated (Box 265, Folder 8)
          - Lesbianism, 1973-76 (Box 266, Folder 1)
          - Literature, media, and the arts, 1970-83 (Box 266, Folder 2-3)
          - Organizing, 1973-83, undated (Box 266, Folder 4)
          - Prison, 1973-81 (Box 266, Folder 5)
          - Rape, 1971-78 (Box 266, Folder 6)
          - Religion, 1972-86 (Box 266, Folder 7)
          - Sports, 1973-83 (Box 266, Folder 8)
          - "Strange" mail, 1974-83, undated (Box 266, Folder 9)
          - Welfare, 1970-75 (Box 267, Folder 1)
          - Women's Movement, 1971-80, undated (Box 267, Folder 2-11)
  - Library
    - Administration
      - Descriptions of holdings for library directories, 1982 (Box 268, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence and memoranda, 1973-83, undated (Box 268, Folder 2-8)
      - Cataloguing: classification systems and processing form (alphabetical by author), 1977-80 (Box 268, Folder 9-17)
      - Collection development: lists of acquisitions, holdings, and subscriptions, 1977 collection policy statement and related correspondence, and purchase orders, 1975-88 (Box 268-269)
      - Evaluation, 1977 (Box 269, Folder 11)
      - Fundraising: notes, correspondence, drafts, and proposals, 1977-80, 1984, undated (Box 269, Folder 12-15)
      - Guide, undated (Box 269, Folder 16)
      - Miscellaneous notes, undated (Box 269, Folder 17)
      - New York women's centers list, undated (Box 270, Folder 1)
      - Personnel policies, 1980, undated (Box 270, Folder 2)
      - Preservation: notes and correspondence, 1978 (Box 270, Folder 3)
      - Procedures: notes, manual draft, periodicals list, research guidelines, 1976-78, undated (Box 270, Folder 4-6)
      - Reports, 1980-81, undated (Box 270, Folder 7)
      - Women's Information Services Network: correspondence, memoranda, surveys, lists, minutes, and reports, 1976-79 (Box 270, Folder 8-12)
      - Women Helping Women Database Project: correspondence, memoranda, invoices, proposals, funding research materials, 1982-87 (Box 270-271)
    - Subject files (Catherine Samuels' files transferred to library)
      - Affirmative Action, 1974-75 (Box 271, Folder 5)
      - AFL-CIO,1975-76, undated (Box 271, Folder 6)
      - Bicentennial: survey of women's participation, undated (Box 271, Folder 7)
      - Economics, 1973-75 (Box 271, Folder 8)
      - Education: inner-city (Boston) women and higher education, circa 1972, and women's studies, 1973, undated (Box 271, Folder 9-10)
    - Employment, 1974-79 (Box 271-272)
      - Media packet, undated (Box 272, Folder 5)
      - Multi-Ethnic Women's Centers Coalition, 1971-72 (Box 272, Folder 6)
      - National Organization for Women, 1980 (Box 272, Folder 7)
      - New York State Division of Human Rights, 1975 (Box 272, Folder 8)
      - "Sex, Power and Politics" syllabus, 1973 (Box 272, Folder 9)
      - State of Women address, undated (Box 272, Folder 10)
      - Women in Leadership, circa 1972 (Box 272, Folder 11)
      - Women in State Government, circa 1975 (Box 272, Folder 12)
    - Reference collections
      - Card files (Box 273-274)
      - Handouts: resource lists and topical bibliographies
        - General (Box 275, Folder 1-2)
        - Bibliographies, circa 1979-81 (Box 275, Folder 3)
        - Subjects
          - Audiovisual materials, undated (Box 275, Folder 4)
          - Battered Women-Employment/Careers, 1977-83 (Box 275, Folder 5)
          - ERA-Grant Sources, 1976-82 (Box 275, Folder 6)
          - History-Public Relations, 1988-89 (Box 275, Folder 7)
          - Rape-Volunteers, 1977-84 (Box 275, Folder 8)
          - Women's Centers-Young Women, 1973-79 (Box 275, Folder 9)
      - New York City Referral System
        - Condensed referral lists, 1977-78 (Box 275, Folder 10)
        - Introduction, 1977 (Box 275, Folder 11)
        - Organizational resource sheets and related literature, alphabetical, circa 1977 (Box 275-276)
      - Vertical files: Organizational resource sheets and related literature
        - Abortion (Box 276, Folder 13-16)
        - Education (Box 276, Folder 17)
        - Employment (Box 276, Folder 18-22)
        - Legal aid (Box 276, Folder 23-26)
        - Legislation (Box 276, Folder 27)
        - Women's centers and programs, general (Box 276, Folder 28)
        - Women's centers and programs: organization profiles, correspondence, brochures, and printed materials, organized by state, also includes Canada and international (Box 276-286)
  - Publications
    - Administration
      - Copyright applications and information (Box 286, Folder 14)
      - Distribution: correspondence, sales records, flow chart, and related material (includes microfiche editions of WAA publications), 1983-86, undated (Box 286, Folder 15-17)
      - Meeting notes, 1980 (Box 286, Folder 18)
      - Proposal, 1976 (Box 286, Folder 19)
      - Report, circa 1975-76 (Box 286, Folder 20)
      - Reprint requests, 1978 (Box 286, Folder 21)
    - Booklets
      - Directory, 1973 (Box 286, Folder 22)
      - Getting Your Share: An Introduction to Fundraising, 1973 (Box 286, Folder 23)
      - How to Make the Media Work for You (Catherine Samuels, 1974) (Box 286, Folder 24)
      - How to Organize a Child Care Center (Carol Shapiro, 1973) (Box 286, Folder 25)
      - How to Organize a Multi-Service Women's Center, 2nd edition, 1976: includes evaluation of original publication, 1974, proposal (Box 286, Folder 26-28)
      - Introduction to the Women's Movement, 1973 (Box 287, Folder 1)
      - Legal Remedies for Tools to Eliminate Sex Discrimination in State and Local Governments (Catherine Samuels, n.d.): correspondence, proposals, research materials, and drafts, 1974-75, undated (Box 287, Folder 2-8)
      - Women and the Human Services: A Checklist (Toby Klass): draft, correspondence, notes by Catherine Samuels, 1973-75 (Box 287, Folder 9)
    - Books
      - The Forgotten Five Million: Women in Public Employment: A Guide to Eliminating Sex Discrimination (1975)
        - Boston Municipal Women's Project: includes notes, "Handbook for Women who Work for the City of Boston," 1974; and "Report on Boston Women's Municipal Employment Project," 1973 (1975) (Box 287-288)
        - Correspondence, includes compliments and reviews, 1972-76 (Box 288, Folder 2-5)
        - Distribution: correspondence, notes, form letters, 1975-76 (Box 288, Folder 6-7)
        - Draft material: "original article, Boston," undated (Box 288, Folder 8)
        - Press release and quote sheets, 1976 (Box 288, Folder 9)
        - Reviews and clippings, 1976 (Box 288, Folder 10)
        - Catherine Samuels, The Forgotten Five Million: Women in Public Employment: A Guide to Eliminating Sex Discrimination (Brooklyn: Faculty Press, 1975) (Box 288, Folder 11)
      - A Practical Guide to the Women's Movement 1975
        - Organizational Resource Sheets (questionnaires), with attached brochures, flyers, etc. (arranged alphabetically by state, followed by the District of Columbia, and International), undated (Box 289, Folder 1-10)
      - Second edition, A (More) Practical Guide to the Women's Movement (1978?): contract, correspondence, proposals, style sheet and miscellany, 1977-80 (Box 290, Folder 1-5)
      - Women's Action Almanac 1980
        - Administration: correspondence, permissions, memoranda, notes, and royalties, 1979-82 (Box 290, Folder 6-11)
        - Distribution and marketing: advertisements, clippings, correspondence, reviews, and lecture tour materials, 1978-82 1980 (Box 288-291)
        - Drafts: includes text and editorial comments, 1978 1980 (Box 291-293)
        - Uncorrected proof, 1980 (Box 293, Folder 6)
      - Women Helping Women, 1981
        - Administration
          - Contracts (includes correspondence, notes and drafts), 1978, 1981 (Box 293, Folder 7-9)
          - Correspondence, 1980-81, undated (Box 294, Folder 1-7)
          - Distribution list, undated (Box 294, Folder 8)
          - Estimates and invoices, 1980-81 (Box 294, Folder 9)
          - Funder information, undated (Box 294, Folder 10)
          - General: notes, 1980-81 (Box 294, Folder 11)
          - Mailing list, undated (Box 294, Folder 12-13)
          - Memoranda and in-house notes, 1980-81 (Box 294, Folder 14)
          - Meeting notes and minutes, 1980-81 (Box 294, Folder 15)
          - Miscellaneous "to do" (Box 294, Folder 16)
          - Notes, 1980-81 (Box 294, Folder 17)
          - Outreach: form letter, undated (Box 294, Folder 18)
          - Proposals, 1980-81, undated (Box 294, Folder 19)
          - Telephone log, undated (Box 295, Folder 1)
          - Jane Williamson's notes, undated (Box 295, Folder 2)
        - Subjects (includes returned questionnaires and attached literature) (Box 295, Folder 3-10)
        - Content
          - Corrections (Box 295, Folder 11)
          - Field testing (Box 295, Folder 12)
          - Notes (Box 295, Folder 13)
          - Drafts (Box 295, Folder 14-18)
          - Back cover copy (Box 295, Folder 19)
          - Second edition: notes and memoranda, 1982-83 (Box 295, Folder 20)
        - Women Helping Women: A State-by-State Directory of Service (New York: Women's Action Alliance, 1981): 2 copies, including Donna Shubert's annotated copy (Box 295, Folder 21-22)
- SERIES IV. PHOTOGRAPHS
  - WAA staff, 1988, 1993-95 (Box 296, Folder 1)
  - Pfizer presentation, 1977 (Box 296, Folder 2)
  - Rockefeller Family Fund report, 1975 (Box 296, Folder 3)
  - Events
    - Celebrating Leadership in Action, 1994-95 (includes Lynn Scherr, Marcia Ann Gillespie, Karel Amarath and Kay Ellen Consolver) (Box 296, Folder 4-5)
    - Project SHARE Walkathon for Breast Cancer, 1994 (Box 296, Folder 6)
    - "Putting the Pieces Together and Shaping the Future," fundraiser, American Museum of Folk Art, 1993 (Box 296, Folder 7)
    - "Putting the Pieces Together: Effective Multi-Cultural Strategies for Reducing Alcohol, Tobacco and Drug Use Among Women and Girls," conference, 1993-95 (Box 296, Folder 8)
    - Second Anniversary of Women and Alcoholism Project, Brunswick House, 1979 (includes Ruth J. Abram) (Box 296, Folder 9)